Class of 1979 Records, 1975-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1979 Records
1975-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1979.
RG 80 UUID:2302fc3d-b377-4684-878a-8841921b51eb
3 boxes (.83 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1979.
The Class of 1979 was the one hundredth and one graduating class of Smith College.
The Class 1979 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1979, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1979 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Yearbook Photographs-unidentified 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 1)
- Yearbook Photographs-houses and groups 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 2)
- Yearbook Photographs-art photographs 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 3)
- Yearbook Photographs-A 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 4)
- Yearbook Photographs-B 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 5)
- Yearbook Photographs-C 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 6)
- Yearbook Photographs-D 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 7)
- Yearbook Photographs-E 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 8)
- Yearbook Photographs-F 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 9)
- Yearbook Photographs-G 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 10)
- Yearbook Photographs-H 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 11)
- Yearbook Photographs-I-J 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 12)
- Yearbook Photographs-K 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 13)
- Yearbook Photographs-L 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 14)
- Yearbook Photographs-M 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 15)
- Yearbook Photographs-N-O 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 16)
- Yearbook Photographs-P 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 17)
- Yearbook Photographs-Q 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 18)
- Yearbook Photographs-R 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 19)
- Yearbook Photographs-S 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 20)
- Yearbook Photographs-T-V 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 21)
- Yearbook Photographs-W 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 22)
- Yearbook Photographs-X-Z 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 23)
- Yearbook Photographs-Staff 1979 (Box 2274, Folder 24)
- Commencement 1979 (Box 2275, Folder 1)
- Commencement Speaker 1979 (Box 2275, Folder 2)
- Freshman Handbook 1975-1976 (Box 2275, Folder 3)
- Freshman Reception 1975 (Box 2275, Folder 4)
- Groups 1975-1979 (Box 2275, Folder 5)
- Ivy Day 1979 (Box 2275, Folder 6)
- Last Chapel 1979 (Box 2275, Folder 7)
- Class Letters 1998-1999 (Box 2275, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1984-1989 (Box 2275, Folder 9)